

# Sirvan Doukchi

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

# **Career Summary**

Full stack developer, with hands-on IT experience, passionate motivated to actualise ideas all the way to implementing in browsers in a userfriendly and modern interface. I am resourceful, and committed to continually advance my knowledge of relevant technologies including JavaScript, React JS/Native, HTML and CSS, Ruby on Rails, Node.JS and more.

Frameworks/Libraries

React.js

Next.js

Vue.is

· Sinatra/PG

Database/Cloud

PostgreSQL

MySQL

Firebase

MongoDB

## Skills

#### Languages

- JavaScript/TypeScript
- · Node.js
- Ruby on Rails
- CSS/SCSS

#### **Techs**

- Docker
- Jira Workflow
- Github Actions
- Adobe Photoshop
- MS Azure
- CISCO CCNA

# Contact



Sydney, New South Wales

www.Sirvan.dev

@sirvan-doukchi

# **Software Engineering Projects**

#### Project 3 - Single page App for media database

- Node JS
- User Authentication
- OMDBI API
- CRUD actions
- · Deployed via Heroku

#### **Project 2 - Melbourne Train Journey Simulation**

- Vanilla JavaScript
- CSS / Bootstrap

#### Project 1 - Tic Tac Toe

- React JS
- Firebase
- Vanilla JavaScript
- CSS / Bootstrap

# **Work Experience**

Clayton UTZ Law Firm

Dec 2020- Sep 2021

#### **IT Support Analyst**

Active directory administration, Microsoft Azure user groups, forest and domain management, shared drives, and application of SCCM, RDP, Logmein, and Skype remote consoles for assisting remote clients.

Melbourne Institue of Technology Oct 2019 - Dec 2020

#### **IT Support Officer**

Liaise with internal staff and students over the phone andon-site utilising HEAT ticket management for level 1 and 2 services and escalation of level 3 and security concerns to infrastructure teams.

### Education

Software Engineering Immersive

#### **General Assembly**

Oct 2021 - March 2022

- · Creating full-stack applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, Express with Node.js, and Version Control (Git and
- Integrated third-party APIs into websites and applications
- Working via remote correspondence and learning new methods of research, communication and collaboration

Masters in Information and Communication Technology

**University of Wollongong** 

Jul 2016 - July 2018

• Post graduated with a distinction average with key subjects: Project and Change Management, Systems Integration, Information Systems and strategy, Strategic network design, IT security and Risk Management.